Time.
From forever.
this.
Do you like Son Ho-young?
Do you like it?
Wow?
What is this?
Do you like Seonho hyung?
Oh, what should I do? Why are you saying this?
Can't you?
Why can't I speak? I like that person. my
He is a partner. Why can't I speak? Wrong
Are you talking? I said it.
Are you crazy? Good job this time, are you timid?
The ugly guy saved you. What what
Even though you know so much.
You have to admit it, it’s in Sun Seon oppa’s ears.
It's just a matter of time.
atmosphere. It's not curry.
No, but even if you trust people, you can’t trust the situation.
I can't do it. I talk without realizing it and get caught.
It could be a situation.
Shall we continue what we were doing? What Seonho oppa knows.
I don't like it, I like it.
I don't like it? Why?
Lay it down. Because it's clear.
It's okay just to think about it. Shop.
okay.
Let's live.
How did you know? Hey, it's weird not to know
It's obvious even if you don't look, how much you shed
I must have been there. I really like just looking at your face
It was a bash. Bring your lunch.
So what did he say?
Don't know? Advice?
Just went away.
Hmm, what was the nuance of saying you like it?
Oh I don't know, you
I was shocked and shocked.
This is what it feels like. Ah,
Look carefully at the sky.
It's like this.
I like it.
It's elegant. Oh, I don't know.
Do you like it more?
I like it. Uh that
You seemed angry.
I'm angry.
That's right, they got angry about that right away.
My sister and brother said it was because they liked each other, but no, it was just that.
As friends, there is a gap between men and women.
14 Between a man and a woman who are having a relationship
I'm angry because they drag the red pepper powder with me, the reality is.
Sibling chemistry is so important to me too.
The only concern is, are you important?
I got angry because I happened to like it
Maybe, huh?
When you need to recognize reality, Napa is the right choice.
What does it mean that a friend is not something that needs to be woken up?
I'm here. Take a good look.
ant.
It doesn't suit me very much, right? Nam Ki-jeong?
Crazy Star Model Bus Oh, I'm crying so much
Even if I build it, I can't help it, Semi
It's science. The reason why I happen to like Namgijang
There's a reason I don't like it even if there isn't one in particular
I don't know enough. If you're a dog model, hey.
Talking to him about me now
No, you're going to feel bad for stopping me, right?
But it's the future. what you said
Is everything correct? Also, did you know that he is a sharpshooter?
Still, sometimes you have to go out of your way.
let's go. uh. Moderately
Do you know that even if you try to guess right, you'll still get nudged?
What ah?
Why did you call me?
ah.
Last night.
If it's awkward, you're weird
You asked. Don’t you like Son again?
Hey, why are you suddenly asking that? People are going to be weird, right?
ah. No, you know.
It's not really something that needs to be explained like this.
Still. you yesterday
I took it as a fait accompli and left angry. me first
I got angry and left. It feels like I did it yesterday so I
Why am I angry no matter who you like?
Why do I have to feel bad?
I said it would have been bad, but somehow I didn't get it?
uh. Then I didn't even say hello yesterday
I went. That's it
Is it because my stomach hurts? You and I
Don’t you know I have irritable bowel syndrome? I don’t know.
Why don't you know that? How did you and I start out?
I should have met him 1000 times if I didn’t have that disease.
I'm just going to ask the woman for tissues. But me
If you have that kind of side to you, take some time off.
I thought I would go around, so I am a hypersensitive person.
I didn't know.
Why are you so smart again?
Oh, you said you were good at studying again, right?
Why are you smiling so strangely? With you
It's easier if you have it, no matter how serious it is
It's amazing that it becomes like nothing.
Well then, I'm glad.
What if? So.
You don’t like Son Ho-young?
Uh huh? Just
Are you a good brother?
Got it? I'm meeting this week
I can’t go because of my part-time job?
uh.
Learn how to lie, kid.
It's okay, the number of lies is increasing.
It was okay, well done.
But you hesitated at one tempo.
Also, I know that Seon-ho likes oppa.
You were shaking.
Ki-jeong got angry and said he needed to learn how to lie.
I was angry when they said it wasn't true, but this is true.
I think so.
Did you do well this time? Of course, being honest and confident
It's the best thing, but it's also a place to lie down
I can't take it off. Being honest and confident
If you become the subject of constant ridicule, you might want to die.
I don't know, but I always put you in the center
Think about it.
Go back to work as usual. preference
Let's leave my brother as my eternal partner.
It’s good, huh?
My heart flutters and sometimes my heart flutters.
uh. uh.
May the island and fruit rest in peace. petulance.
said.
Man, this is a revelation from God. let's have a beer
How are you doing? Carl, there's still time left until the deadline.
Hurry up and start me, yeah, this is it
Configure it? Yes.
Let's do it again. Let's do it again.
hmm.
hey. Ah
Ah ya ah wait a minute ah still
Aren’t you just avoiding it? Fortunately
There's no bleeding. Take care like this.
I wake up after seeing it. ah.
You lose to me too. so.
uh.
Hey Seonho.
Coffee has been delivered. Here is my first-year junior, Kang Ji-won.
It's called Guseono. Green is close to his friend
Do you look more handsome now? Ah, the word
Take it easy. Don't even talk. I
I'm so crazy about wanting to become friends with my brother.
I got into a bit of trouble. True
He is a rare and cute younger brother.
Our Myung-Hoon is also a really good younger brother.
I want to be a good guy, not a good younger brother.
Myung-hoon, listen carefully. The good man in my life is
None. There are only good friends, good brothers and sisters.
That's it. I can't touch it
If you protect it, I will protect it. Don’t worry, sister.
Total girl crush. No hands are visible.
It's not like that, how can I strictly protect it?
If you want to protect it, you have to protect it, not the downward polarity.
This is. Uh, as a good man rather than just a good younger brother.
I want to be seen. Something like that.
I promised to cancel and work again
It's there, hey, why aren't you worried?
It's okay to get over it because it's there to get over it.
It's there to protect you.
a little. That's
Hey, we made the original promise too
I'll go. Teacher, I will see you more and more. Senior
Hey, stop giving it to me. tomorrow
See you. Come quickly.
I am.
Ah, but it suits you really well.
Do Seon-ho, go home.
If I take you there, you will return.
It's early evening and I haven't even had a drink.
Only when I was sucked was the evening flight
Transformer. Hmm.
Oh, it's okay, if you look at me like that, you'll lose your arms and legs
What happens?
Ah, I'll do it later when I visit your wife.
Yeah. What if I ask you and then take it away and send it to you? You have to work hard
If you can't use it, you send it to me.
You're the enemy, aren't you?
Do it this time.
I'm in my pocket anyway
What are you doing with the card?
See you tomorrow my friend Seonho.
What should I say about this week’s concept? diverse opinions
Tae Hwan-young Oh, it’s time to find Talks Club and start again.
Gone Together No Comments It's fun.
also.
But why doesn’t Sunwoo oppa say anything?
But why don’t you tell me you’re full?
When it's decided
I'll follow you. where is it
That doesn't work. Let's give him a penalty. This time I'm full
Jeong Hae Woo.
Come on. and.
why?
Nam Ki-jeong, you have no opinion. Where did you get the money from this?
Hit it?
The regulations don't say anything.
one side.
It's a real game, now uh yeah
Game summary? Why? First of all,
Others dot dot.
Sorry, you two.
I have to do it.
Hey, are you on the phone right now?
It's really transparent.
yes?
Where are you going?
Ki-jeong.
Why did I see this week's concept in a Spanish group chat?
Has an important mission to decide fallen on me?
hey. What's important about the country? you
What? Are you exhibiting at the Vinale?
Anything else, at least stand on the academy red carpet
Or at least direct the Grammy stage.
no. So far I
I've never led anything, so no,
That's not it. Will I disappoint you?
Look. Everyone says it's not good
What if I do it? I can't do anything
What if I say it’s good? Then it's a nuisance, you idiot.
It's a fucking nuisance. hey.
The concept itself is made of bad things.
So that's okay, right? uh? Then the worse it is, the better.
Everyone puts their energy into what they think is the best
There are some things that aren't that good, but hey.
And look at the green pig first. what
No matter what disappointment you bring, the leaders are there
Does it exist? What's wrong?
What is it that makes you so curious every time?
Shout out anything.
Is that why you did it? Well, I was talking to you on the phone.
I told you why I wanted to do it. When I talk to you, everything
All problems become easier.
When I talk to this, I become really strong.
I feel like it. Although there is no basis. you
Is it really Miracle?
thank you. what to do
Have you decided? Got it?
Hang up, reporter. Why why?
Are you really not mad?
you. you really
Don’t you like Sun Seon-hyung?
With words.
no. okay?
I'm not angry either. Hang up.
ah.
Oh, I forgot, but I brought it up again.
I saw it.
What is it? Son Ho-young, who do you like a lot?
Who is Seonho-young? He is my older sister’s friend.
Like the picture. Then who
I like it, but hey, a pot belly is a seafood stew.
I just like you
That's why I felt bad
You shouldn't graduate, you shouldn't graduate
Son Ho-young is said to like penis.
Why?
I can, but why does this make me feel bad?
Hey, that's right, I'm your older sister. and
Of course, I feel a little bad too.
It can happen. Hey, think about it.
What are you guys?
Do you like customers?
absolutely. So I feel like
It was bad. no
It's not really like this, we
We're friends. It's not really. What
It's a sound.
What is my concept?
I have never tried anything in my life.
There will be nothing else to do in the future.
It definitely looks like it's going to fail.
Go to
g. yes.
Yes, once before I die
Let's do it. Culcus.
uh.
I'm ready to transform, Baek.
It's just a unicorn. It's too cute.
It's cool hey.
I think this is better,
Yes. grass. This
No.
B.L. What am I?
what? I'm sure it's a girl crush, but?
It's cuter than the hair.
Wait, I'll give it a try.
It suits you so well. What do you think? first time
I'm trying it out and I think it's good.
Oh, and when I see it too
It's cool, hit it. No. No no no
Uh huh?
Actually, I've never really done any shopping before.
None.
How about the land?
Um, it's pretty, cute, shopping with the kids
Even if I go, I can’t buy mine.
He used to come here often and always agreed with me.
End song z You're going crazy.
I told you it was pretty. Wear it.
Even if I see clothes I like, no, they're not with me
I think it would suit me.
That's why clothes always don't look like me
I only bought what caught my eye.
Why do you like it so much?
I just saw it because it was pretty.
I wanted to try it on like this once. Then try it on
Do you have to wear clothes to know? No.
I've never worn something like this before, so I'm going to try this.
Isn't it a little strange? No, dinner.
I like it.
yes. Absolutely. That's it. shopping
Done. I'll wear this and go. wait a minute.
Why is there a problem with my stomach?
I was thinking of buying something more affordable. Anyway
I don't think I'll wear it well
You came from the future. Giving up in advance is that.
It's a habit, so what? Just try it on once
Beggar eggplant. what are you doing like that
Are you all worried? Just scream.
then. I will wear it like this.
yes.
Hanawa Jeon enters port
Is dispatch ya a model? Awesome
It's so pretty hey hey
It's not him. that
Really.
Is this ridiculous?
That's good, I just brush it off when I'm alone.
But my wife didn't contact me, so I'm alone today.
It doesn't come out, hey, I just texted you
I can't come out today.
Oh, I'm so annoyed, I'll have to wait.
Okay next pussy try cheap model is it?
Let’s sell it like this and try to break it, shall we?
Oh, I guess it was a bit easy. Oh, how many times has this happened?
Take a break already because you filmed it. Let's just fight ah
Yes, LB doesn't say a word, but it's hot. oh
Man, really, really, I'm talking about the boss.
When I asked if he was crying or coming, I was like, is this not coming or is it coming?
Just take a 5 minute break
I guess that's because I have a lot of time, I guess.
Start.
Just Mr.
Unrequited love number 1 made no progress
A bloody fight between two siblings over a man.
It's heartbreaking, but it's not funny.
I have it, but I lose. But Seonyoung and writing
Dice are quite old. No, middle school
They said they've been friends since then. Hey
Are you still overflowing with nowhere to go?
You didn’t confess, right? Oh no.
Don't do that, just don't do that, just that
Can't you? Then, in fear of getting hit, I put it in the closet.
Just tell me to hit you in the head and get out.
Just.
I confessed and it was a surprise.
Oh, I really want to keep doing this, it’s really not fun.
What's not fun? What kind of brother is Jijeong?
Do you like it?
Yes, it has been established?
cell phone. Is it broken?
Oh, stop looking at selfies.
Aren’t you going to keep sending it to me because you don’t reply?
Why don't you reply when I ask if it's a lipo? no why
ask me You'll know when you see me, right?
Because I like it when my brother talks to me, right?
brother. How many times are left 40
Why fire?
I can get it done in 30 minutes, it's awesome. That's really
He's so awesome. Who are you? Finish it.
I'll do whatever I have to do. Even if you fold your arms, you can do all the shoulder work.
If you spend more than you want, can you pose?
Oh good, see you next time.
okay.
Oh, is it good?
It's good to drink.
Just a little bit.
Okay, it came out.
came out End like today
I hung up. Okay huh?
Maybe hey, I should go see my brother. It’s late.
Where are you going?
Why are you so busy?
I really don't know what to say?
Even if I just look at it
I accidentally tasted my fingertips.
Two are in the kidneys
I even wore a pink hairpiece
I really want to understand.
That's it. us
I'll be there first.
Rainfall and.
I waited a long time, you
Good. I'm sorry because it's my first time
I don't know what it is. just
I just enjoy playing.
I expressed it.
Cold too.
He said he didn't know about my part-time job today.
Did you finish quickly?
how is it? Not much of a marketing concept
Concept. What kind of concept is this?
There's nothing like a goal cross that's given to me.
Where are you, how are you? Do you only do content?
I don’t know, Ki-jeong is here?
You said you didn’t know?
Why am I coming down again?
hello. Woohyun and I feel like today
It's similar.
Lift it up. Really?
My sisters decorated it for me.
Let's go, full stomach.
Hey, where are you? Where are you?
Isn't it here?
It's so bright and suits you so well?
Who doesn't know? Pretending to be popular
Pay some money and go.
How about coming out? prank
No, it's not a joke
Really.
liberation.
What are you doing? This is the concept, cold
It's in. Show while working.
ah.
Oh I.
Well, I think that's kind of true, yeah.
Shall we take a look?
Hey, get out of here
I'm in trouble.
Hey, I saved this in my sketchbook.
Is your pencil broken?
Oh, I'm using salt, huh?
Okay, Japan is over.
and. That's right. Don't worry
The cosplay was really good.
If you draw a hundred, where is it?
hmm. Why are you doing this?
I really can't like it
I drew it, it's okay, it's okay, it's not
It was okay, but not for long.
Of course, right? And I told you what.
Still, it doesn't matter.
what's the matter?
Listen carefully. good at drawing
What's more important than confidence is confidence, understand?
Everyone gather around.
Sister, stop it. Okay, stop.
see.
Oh, the line is powerful
Do you have it?
Well, surprisingly, the painting is safe for the price tag.
I thought it was, but why the price?
The sense of need is also good. It's not much
It's really amazing.
The confused inside is very clear
It was expressed. Of course, the storm and fury of adolescence
Timing Yes. practical skills
Will it be big? Will it be?
There's no way, no, there's no way that's possible. no
I wonder what happened to everyone.
What and where is this? It's in Korean, but even drawing this
It's bouncy and I'm good at drawing it as something I buy.
I guess so.
Hey, why don't you give up?
Hey, really, really.
Is Green right?
That's a good drawing. I get 100 for 1 month
I haven't been able to lift a single hand in a while, should I show you this?
ruler.
Ah. uh
Here.
and. today today
Is there coloring too? time is 2000 won
I tried painting something with the leftovers.
I still feel like my hands are too weak. Still, better than me
Better. Oh I
You can't complete it. exactly in a month
They said I couldn't boil them one by one, so I boiled my face instead.
You draw really well. i draw faces
This is really fun, right?
Hippo stores all have different facial expressions. That
If you look hard, you will lose concentration
It's just so much fun.
So, some more khaki hats
Let's go, okay, just make a face.
Let's see, it might be a bad thing
No, everyone really likes pictures.
A group of people who draw?
Please take a look at the picture I worked so hard on
Are you laughing at me because I can’t draw? This is the worst.
Really? I
There's nothing different about him.
After the couple pose is over, who will do it?
Today, I'm with Wooyeon and Seonho over there.
Why not give it a try? They look like a couple
Oh, it's fresh.
So is that right?
yes.
Oh Yeon-ah.
I'll do it.
A jacket that says I'm in a relationship with a pot-bellied guy
Please lend me some, why is the press conference
It would suit you better, right?
ruler.
eww.
Can you call that Australia?
Hey, Nam Gyu-jeong, try to be nice to yourself.
My favorite model is so stiff, why?
How to do it better and do it naturally.
yes.
uh.
uh. uh.
Today too, a true masterpiece is born.
I'm a model. With my sister
The two don't get along well
I like this the most: bathroom
Men's brown hete discovery, everyone is doing well
You don't know the pain, but I actually
Sangnamsa Temple is an example of the times. yes.
I also attracted less.
I went in.
I know Green sister well.
What time?
So what about an affair?
Well, I'm Grimmy tell me. preference
What do I remember about the manly body?
doesn't exist?
No matter how much I think about it, I am a member.
I have never been a manly man. black
Nope. Almost every day
And what about Namdong?
what? So where did you go? child?
I really don't know, actually.
yes.
What's wrong? Couple with Jeon Yong
Are you mad because I couldn’t fake the pose? What?
Do I have to answer what or
I memorized it and you said you wouldn't come.
Seonho oppa.
I told you I didn't like it.
But I don't believe it. Are you here to monitor me?
Let me ask you just one question. I?
If you like Sunwoo oppa, why not?
Don't let anyone tell you it can't be done?
If I like Seonho oppa, why do you do this?
country.
You saw Creon and Dr. Seon-ok's I'll Try It. however.
How do I prevent this?
How do I fit in among them?
Look, no, yes, how good are you with your sister and brother Son?
Do you know better than anyone else whether you suit each other?
Did you come running because you thought I might confess?
How can I do that?
If you confess it.
That you can't just look at it, that's it
How well do you know?
Why would you do such a stupid thing?
So, Kijeong.
Is it okay for me not to monitor you? You are your sister.
Just as I am important, I am also important.
Why would I go when I can clearly see the path to getting hurt?
uh.
Do you like my brother?
Until now, I'll just like it with my heart.
Whether I like someone or not is up to me, so.
Don't get into my mind.
eww.
Also, the at-home example unfolds earlier.
It's the same there. what about you
A child?
Pinch hitter.
No, no, but how many heretics do you have?
Are you sitting there holding on to your years? like a brother
I ended up leaving. You can study alone. So
My mom even gave me a reading room. fruit again
Paste it. No,
Can you do it alone?Last time
The test went up a bit, right? Is that right?
Is that difficult?
Should mom just give up, is that better?
Do everything in reverse.
yes. why are you today
Did you come? You said you wouldn't come?
I know.
I don't know either. Seonho oppa.
I told you I didn't like it.
But I don't believe it. Are you here to monitor me?
No, if I like Seonho oppa, why are you doing this?
country.
Please talk to me. Why on earth did I
Am I angry? Did I try something between Creon and Seon?
Because I saw it. But that's not it. How can I be liberated?
How do I get involved with them?
Let me ask you just one question.
Why don't I like Sunho oppa?
Is it okay?
Answer me. Why not?
If you don't come to the Galleria by 5:30, wait.
Hello? Uh
I'm not going.
necessary.
What the hell?
Hyuna.
You're right on time.
He said he was suffering from emphysema and suddenly took a picture of the gallery.
They said they were sending it for you because you were sick, so they came.
Isn’t that right? Uh.
It's a regulation.
Oh, it's okay. Didn't you tell Wooyeon?
Um, okay, okay, wait a minute.
Next, Jeon Ho-young, do you like going to small galleries?
I don't date green pigs.
The two of them are just two children on the mountain. I
How many years have you changed?
Don't worry. Don't worry.
Stop liking things only with your heart.
and. yesterday
I was sorry.
And again. you lied
He was good at it. If you talk to me
You say it's good to be simple?
But even though you were with me yesterday, I thought about you a lot
It was a lot and complicated.
Ask Sun Seon to buy you something delicious. shoulder
Smoke some. hmm.
Did you have a good call? Then
Shall we go in?
uh.
Was it fun?
yes.
Why is it not good?
No, was it fun?
Hey brother.
I have something to ask.
wait for a sec.
Get it. The picture is messed up again
Come and take me away. They say it's getting cold in the evening.
I'll go, hold on tight to you.
If it happens, I'll have to go. So again
I guess it's rude.
yes. Please hurry up, I'm sorry.
I asked Shinsin to go to the regulations and buy him food. no.
Don't worry then
See you at the meeting.
Jo Hyeon-ah.
Will it get colder later?
No, it's okay, just go. It has to be like this, my heart
I did it because I thought it would be comfortable.
uh.
I'm going, go in carefully?
Blockinger is a great person.
Sorry, just a moment
Do you have something like me?
The person who looked at me at a glance.
The size is perfect. how is it?
Helped me step into a new world
People. cool
People like nice people.
Of course.
My heart dares to like a wonderful person.
then. It's my heart.
I told my descendants not to call anyone.
It wasn't because I passed it on and changed it. I can tell anyone
I do it to anyone. They say they just want to take me there
Don't even do that. Oh me too
Because I don't have an evening flight anymore.
Are you going to pretend to come out? Ha.
I can't do it, sister. I'll give you a hangover cure in Seoul, so here you go.
Just wait.
and. uh.
what?
They say they don’t like me because I’m fat.
No matter what and modern.
Are you saying I’m going to lose weight?
you are getting stronger
Even though I know you're following me, you keep your mouth shut.
Do you feel like you are being escorted?
Incheon Chana.
What happened to Son Ho-young? Why did he just leave?
I asked you to feed me food?
Oh, really? Why?
no. you
I don't know how we got involved.
I don't have to worry about you?
What did I do to you yesterday? You
Isn't it because of me?Is it because of me?
Not once do I have it on the floor
There are days when I feel like a ten-won coin rolling around.
Ten won worth.
Did you pick that up?
Look, no one is giving it?
Even ten won is money, but no one cares or looks at it, so it’s useless.
That means there isn't one. It's funny, but
I'm thinking of giving it a try, so I wonder if 15 would be okay.
I don't know, it's live. 10-10 won but
Even as you age in your 20s, 30s, and 40s,
What if it's a ten-won coin?
Have you ever thought of something like that?
Even. I'm a blank check and the boss type.
As expected, Nam Gyu-jeong makes it easy.
You know what?
you are pretty uh.
Put it in my eyes? Is it pretty now?
Listen, mom.
My sister hasn't come home yet?
Why, what's wrong, mom?
But there was no sound?
I never went in and never left.
Huh?
No, don't meet him at this time. Don't come home.
I'm surprised. One week like that.
You already know.
Now that happens to say
Got it, yes. I was in a bad mood
Why?
No beta.
like me
Don't use your hand for fear of hitting it.
ever so.
But now I know it's you
I felt it right away. How long does it last?
fate person daam do
Shinsegae was surprised to find me, right?
What else is right? Listing
Cebu's eldest son became Spanish
Son Ho-young, who said he would be grateful.
Won't I be a man with you? I'm not friends with you
Isn’t that kind of responsible?
If there's a kid in your class who isn't good enough, make friends too.
He's so handsome, he's over there again.
Why does such an ordinary year look so good?
It suits you really well and I also do skinship.
Exercise even if you are independent. Let's get married.
I don’t study because I’m told to grow up.
do. No, just wait
Do you buy 50 all the time? Totally.
I don't study because I'm told to do it.
Someone told me to come into my sister’s room, so go out.
This times eight is 56 times
Living.
48 345 times five hundred and ten
It’s 176,640, right? Don’t you know that either?
Ah, I'm tired after playing with the idiot.